var triviaQuestions = [
    {
        askedQuestion: "1 2 or 3",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "1",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "4 5 or 6",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "7 8 or 9",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "1 2 or 3",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "1",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "4 5 or 6",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "7 8 or 9",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "1 2 or 3",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "1",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "4 5 or 6",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "7 8 or 9",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        askedQuestion: "7 8 or 9",
        avalibleChoices: ["1","2","3"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
];
